BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 100-110 (Box 65)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Saint Louis Southwestern, 1963-1965 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Louis Southwestern (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Texarkana Union Station Trust, 1933-1967 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Saint Louis Southwestern, 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Texas and Pacific, 1962-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis - By-Laws, 1964-1974 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis, 1964-1975 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Illinois Terminal Railroad Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis - Patrolmen, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Joint Agency, National Stock Yards, Illinois, 1951-1968 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific Lines East, 1969-1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    May 1, 1969-April 1973
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Joseph Terminal Railroad Company, 1921-1968 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific Lines East (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1973 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Joseph Terminal Railroad Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific, Lines East, 1967-1969 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    January 1967-April 29, 1969
  - Boards of Adjustment - Wabash, 1963-1966 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Tidewater Plumas Community Hospital, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Board of Adjustment - Western Pacific Railroad Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - Tidewater Southern Railway, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Board of Adjustment - Sacramento Northern Railway (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Sacramento Northern Railway Board of Adjustment, 1947-1963 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Alameda Belt Line Board of Adjustment, 1947-1969 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Board of Adjustment - Western Pacific - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report of General Chairman, System Board Number 109, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    April 1, 1973-March 31, 1974
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1967-1973 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- 111-121 (Box 66)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Portland Terminal Railroad Company, 1963-1973 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Portland Terminal Railroad Company - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Florida East Coast, 1960-1971 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Consolidated, 1966-1973 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Norfolk Southern Railway Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1969 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Consolidated - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic and East Carolina Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1967 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Greyhound Line - Board of Adjustment, 1953-1970 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Stock Yards District Agency Board of Adjustment, 1940-1959 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Saint Paul Union Depot System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1964 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Saint Paul Union Depot (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Waukegan North Chicago Transit Company Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Board of Adjustment - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago Railways' Hotel Ticket Offices, 1947-1968 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Illinois Northern Railway Board of Adjustment, 1949-1959 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago Union Station Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago, West Pullman, and Southern, 1948-1969 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Chicago, North Shore and Milwaukee System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1959 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Chicago South Shore and South Bend Board of Adjustment, 1935-1963 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chicago and Western Indiana - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Board of Adjustment, 1932-1959 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Board of Adjustment - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Western Indiana (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1974 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago Union Station, 1965-1969 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau, 1961-1973 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Board of Adjustment - North Pacific Coast Freight Bureau, 1955-1968 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- 122-152 (Box 67)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio (Pere Marquette District), 1963-1969 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1967-1969 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Toledo Terminal Railroad - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Board of Adjustment - Freight Forwarding, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Board of Adjustment - Freight Forwarding, 1970-1973 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - System Board of Adjustment - Freight Forwarding - By-Laws, 1960-1971 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - L.E. Dennis - Freight Forwarding Board of Adjustment, 1964-1970 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Freight Forwarding, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Freight Forwarding, 1967-1969 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Panda Terminals, Incorporated, 1967-1969 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Springmeier Shipping Company, Incorporated Board of Adjustment, 1957-1967 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - ABC Freight Forwarding Board of Adjustment, 1959-1971 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Acme Fast Freight Board of Adjustment, 1953-1971 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Acme Delivery Service, Incorporated (Denver, Colorado) Board of Adjustment, 1963-1971 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Lifschultz Fast Freight Board of Adjustment, 1957-1971 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - International Forwarding Company Board of Adjustment, 1957-1971 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Empire Household Shipping Company of New York, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - National Carloading Board of Adjustment, 1957-1971 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Universal Carloading and Distributing Board of Adjustment, 1957-1971 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Republic Carloading Company Board of Adjustment, 1959-1971 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Transportation Company, 1965-1971 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Boards of Adjustment - WFA Trucking Company, 1965-1971 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Dorcar, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Boston and Maine Transportation Company Board of Adjustment, 1957-1966 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific, Lines West, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific, Lines West, 1965-1968 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Spokane Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1926-1966 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Overland Terminal Warehouse Company - Los Angeles, California Board of Adjustment, 1952-1970 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Employees Hospital Association Board of Adjustment, 1958-1970 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Yakima Valley Transportation Company Board of Adjustment, 1958-1970 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Spokane International Railway Company Board of Adjustment, 1955-1970 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Board of Adjustment - Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Board of Adjustment - Union Pacific, Lines West (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 37)
- 153-202 (Box 68)
  - System Board of Adjustment Number 163 - Annual Report, 1970-1972 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    July 1, 1970-June 30, 1972
  - Board of Adjustment - Long Island (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1973 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - United Transport Service Employees General Executive Board Meeting, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    September 17, 1972. Bound.
  - The Eighteenth Biennial Constitutional Convention of United Transport Service Employees, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    September 17-19, 1972. Bound.
  - System Board of Adjustment - Puerto Rico International Airlines, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canton Railroad - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Galveston Wharves - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Board of Adjustment - Long Island, 1962-1969 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    June 1, 1962 - December 31, 1969
  - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1955-1959 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Bush Terminal Company, 1959-1961 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - New York Dock Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Reading Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Reading Company, 1966-1969 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Clinchfield, 1961-1974 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - Clinchfield Railroad Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Western Maryland - By-Laws, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Board of Adjustment - Western Maryland, 1970-1974 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Maryland, 1963-1969 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Western Maryland Warehouse Company Board of Adjustment, 1958-1971 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Board of Adjustment - Western Maryland Railway Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Maryland - Patrolmen, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Board of Adjustment - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown, 1960-1973 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Bessemer and Lake Erie, 1961-1975 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Board of Adjustment - Bessemer and Lake Erie (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Board of Adjustment - Bessemer and Lake Erie - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Illinois Midland, 1963-1972 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Board of Adjustment - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Chicago and Illinois Midland System Board of Adjustment - Civil Action 3202 (Chicago and Illinois Midland versus Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen et al), 1963- 1965 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Board of Adjustment - New Orleans Public Belt, 1940-1974 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - New Orleans System Boards of Adjustment 202 and 213 - Appeal: C.G. Mitchell, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- 163-263-0 (Box 69)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Terminals, Limited, 1966-1970 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Canadian National (Newfoundland Division), 1963-1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Special File Compiled by C.L. Dennis, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    August 1973
  - Board of Adjustment - Long Island, 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - Reading Company - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Philadelphia, Bethlehem, and New England, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Koppers Company, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Reading Transportation Company Board of Adjustment, 1946-1972 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Board of Adjustment - Reading Company, 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Board of Adjustment - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Board of Adjustment - Buck's Airport Service, 1961-1968 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Allied Aviation Service Company of California, 1958-1968 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Board of Adjustment - Allied Maintenance Corporation of Nevada, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Ward Sky Cap Porter Service, 1965-1968 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - System Division Express, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    September 12, 1974-March 19, 1975
  - System Division Express, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    June 14, 1974-September 11, 1974
  - Disaster Relief (Financial Assistance) - Contributions, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    March-April 1971
  - Disaster Relief (Financial Assistance) - Contributions, 1967-1971 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    January 1967-February 1971
- 203-249 (Box 70)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Delaware and Hudson, 1963-1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Delaware and Hudson Railroad (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, 1970-1973 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    January 1970-January 1973
  - Board of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Pittsburgh and West Virginia Divisions, 1966-1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Nickel Plate District, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Delaware and Hudson - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Board of Adjustment, 1957-1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Nickel Plate District, 1962-1970 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Wabash District, 1967-1971 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Norfolk District, 1967-1969 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Norfolk District, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Norfolk District (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Wabash Employees Hospital Association System Board of Adjustment, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Norfolk and Western, Norfolk District - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line Board of Adjustment, 1956-1970 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - New Jersey-Indiana-Illinois Board of Adjustment, 1959-1971 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    October 1959-November 1971
  - System Board of Adjustment - Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range, Soo Line, 1921-1965 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Joint Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range, Soo Line - Patrolmen, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Boards of Adjustment - (Joint) Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range, Soo Line, 1965-1969 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- 218-284-38 (Box 71)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Consolidated Norfolk and Western, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    February 8, 1973-September 1974
  - State Legislation - Maryland, 1956-1970 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - State Legislation - Massachusetts, 1965-1967 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - State Legislation - Michigan, 1964-1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - State Legislation - Minnesota, 1965-1970 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Includes bound materials.
  - State Legislation - Mississippi, 1955-1971 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi Labor Council's Program for Progress (Box 71, Folder 7)
    No date.
  - State Legislation - Missouri, 1965-1971 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - State Legislation - Montana, 1954-1970 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - State Legislation - Nebraska, 1963-1966 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - State Legislation - Nevada, 1937-1971 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Provincial Legislation - Newfoundland, Canada, 1960-1961 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - State Legislation - New Hampshire, 1934-1970 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - State Legislation - New Jersey, 1966-1968 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - State Legislation - New Mexico, 1951-1970 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - State Legislation - New York, 1963-1971 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - State Legislation - North Carolina, 1957-1967 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- 250-459 (Box 72)
  - Board of Adjustment - Tennessee Central (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Board of Adjustment - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency (RPIA), 1966-1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Fruit Growers Express Company Board of Adjustment, 1947-1969 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Western Warehousing Company Board of Adjustment, 1940-1971 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Pacific and Atlantic Shippers Association Incorporated Board of Adjustment, 1957 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau, 1943-1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - The Alaska Railroad (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Northwest Airlines, 1963-1972 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Miami Area: Avianca, Incorporated District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Boards of Adjustment - New York Area: Avianca, Incorporated District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Avianca, Incorporated, 1964-1966 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - The Toronto, Hamilton and Buffalo Railway Company (Transportation Communication Union), 1969-1974 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Capital Airlines System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines, Incorporated System Board of Adjustment (Capital Airlines), 1956-1961 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    1956-May 31, 1961
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees (System Board of Adjustment 451) - The Modern Union on the Move, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Western Airlines, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Western Air Lines Board of Adjustment, 1947-1957 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees (System Board of Adjustment 451) - The Modern Union on the Move, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- 460-505 (Box 73)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Pullman, 1961-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Allied Aviation Service Company Board of Adjustment, 1954-1967 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Boards of Adjustment Express, 1965-1973 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Allegheny District (Express) - By-Laws, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Allegheny District (Express), 1966-1974 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - Texas and Louisiana Department (Express), 1967-1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Board of Adjustment - Texas and Louisiana Department (Express), 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Board of Adjustment - Trans-Missouri District (Express), 1962-1974 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Board of Adjustment - Trans-Missouri District (Express) - By-Laws, 1962-1974 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Kansas and Oklahoma (Midwest District), 1963-1974 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - boards of Adjustment - Kansas and Oklahoma (Midwest District) - By-Laws, 1963-1974 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Board of Adjustment - Kansas and Oklahoma District (Midwest); BWS-AIR Delivery, Kansas City, Missouri, 1968-1972 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- 506-510 (Box 74)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Atlantic Department District board, 1967-1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting, South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    June 15, 1974
  - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1963-1966 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Atlantic Department District Board - By-Laws, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Atlantic Department District Board - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Bound. June 20, 1970
  - South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    June 16, 1973. Bound.
  - Boards of Adjustment - Empire District (REA Express), 1963-1974 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    June 21, 1969. Bound.
  - South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    June 22, 1968. Bound.
  - Boards of Adjustment - Empire District (REA Express) - By-Laws, 1963-1974 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Central Pacific Department (REA Express), 1963-1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Central Pacific Department (REA Express) - By-Laws, 1963-1974 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Board of Adjustment - Northern District (Express), 1974 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - Northern District (Express) - By-Laws, 1962-1974 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Northern District (Express), 1962-1973 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Gulf (Express) Department, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Board of Adjustment - Gulf Department (Express), 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Board of Adjustment - Gulf Department (Express), 1966 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Gulf (Express) Department - By-Laws, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Board of Adjustment - Gulf Department (Express), 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- 511-516 (Box 75)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District (Express), 1972-1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District (Express), 1967-1972 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    1967-May 5, 1972
  - Board of Adjustment - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District (Express) - By-Laws, 1972-1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District (Express), 1963-1966 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Board of Adjustment - New England District (Express), 1967-1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Board of Adjustment - New England District (Express) - By-Laws, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Boards of Adjustment - New England District (Express), 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Boards of Adjustment - New York District (REA Express), 1963-1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Boards of Adjustment - AALCO Consolidations, Incorporated (REA - New York District), 1965-1974 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Boards of Adjustment - New York District (REA Express) - By-laws, 1963-1974 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Pacific District (Express), 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Pacific District (Express) - By-Laws, 1971-1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Boards of Adjustment - South Pacific District (Express), 1962-1970 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Southwestern Department (Express), 1974 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Board of Adjustment - Southwestern Department (Express), 1967-1973 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Board of Adjustment - Southwestern Department (Express) - By-Laws, 1967-1974 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Boards of Adjustment - Southwestern Department (Express), 1963-1966 (Box 75, Folder 17)